https://www.carbodydesign.com/info/privacy/

Sign In
Home (new server)
News Archives
Design News Wall (NEW!)
From the Archive
How to Draw Cars: 3/4 View Dynamic Sketch by Arvind Ramkrishna
Car Design Schools
A selection of well-known design schools from around the world that offer Courses in Transportation Design.
News Archives
Design News Wall (NEW!)
Monthly Archive
Database
Google Search
Privacy Policy (GDPR)Information pursuant to Art. 13 of the European Regulation n. 679/2016 (GDPR) and pursuant to the national legislation regarding the protection of personal data.
Data Controller
The data controller is:
Line22 SRL
Via Paul Cezanne 11 – 00178 Rome – VAT IT 11629321008
The data controller can be contacted at any time at info@carbodydesign.com
Why do we collect information
Information collected is used to:
Improve the user experience and provide you with content tailored to your needs and interests
Monitor how the site is used so that we can continually improve it.
Give you access to certain features of the website (such as commenting)
Send you updates through an email newsletter
Processing methods
Personal data are processed in compliance with the principles of
lawfulness, correctness and transparency. The processing of your personal data is carried
out by means of the following operations: collection, registration, organization, structuring,
storage, consultation, adaptation or modification, use, dissemination, communication,
extraction, comparison, interconnection, limitation, deletion and destruction of data. Your
personal data are processed exclusively in digital format.
We have taken safety and protection measures, including data encryption, and strong password policies on all machines which contains such data. We also establish partnerships only with reliable, law-compliant third parties with regards to the web hosting and newsletter services.
Collected Data
Cookie
Some data are automatically collected through cookies because of users’ actions on the website. For more information please check our Cookie Policy
Website Statistics – Google Analytics
This website uses Google Analytics to track the number of visits, the pages visited and other metrics, which allow us to analyze traffic and review aggregated statistics.
In order to make sure that no PII (Personal Identifiable Information) are collected by Google Analytics, we have enabled the IP anonymization and disabled the “User ID” feature that could track individual users.
Advertising
This website is supported by advertising, i.e. sponsored ads displayed in the form of graphic elements (banners) and/or textual ads.
We are running both ads by direct advertisers through the Google DoubleClick server, and other ads from the Google AdSense network.
To better ensure our users’ privacy protection, we have disabled the interest-based ads that rely on information related to the users’ personal preferences and/or previous navigation.
Our ads are purely contextual, which means that they depend exclusively on the topic of the various pages and on a limited set of information about the users – such as country of origin, language and or type of device. These are generic, anonymized data that cannot be considered as PII (personal identifiable information).
However for statistical purposes the data collected by Google Analytics could be linked with the data collected by Google AdSense and/or DoubleClick for Publishers, which could potentially enable the user’s identification
To know more about Google’s privacy policy, and how to disable the personal data tracking, please refer to the page https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/partner-sites/
Contact Form
By filling in the contact form(s) the user allows the use of the provided information to carry out the requested service (quotation, information request or other), in the same way as when sending a regular email.
The type of data requested – mandatory or optional – is indicated in the form itself.
Collected data may include: first name, last name, country, address, website URL and other data depending on the particular request or form
Personal data collected through contact forms are NOT STORED in any database, but forwarded to an email address and processed exactly like a regular email.
Newsletter
Registration to our newsletter is carried out by filling a form. The service is activated through an opt-in process: the user is required to click on an activation link sent via email by our newsletter automation service.
Newsletter Data Processor
To ensure a high quality service we use a proven third party service to manage our newsletter and relative data:
AWeber Systems, Inc. – United States
Personal Data Management
Collected data can include email, name and country.
The newsletter tracking process could also collect data relative to the interaction between the user and the newsletter: hours, email opens, clicks on links.
Users can subscribe at any moment by simply clicking on the unsubscribe link which is included at the bottom of each newsletter. It’s also possible to send a direct email to info@carbodydesign.com asking to unsubscribe and/or to delete all personal data.
Time of conservation
The Data Controller will process personal data for the time necessary to fulfill the
purposes highlighted above.
Subjects and categories of subjects to whom the data may be communicated
In addition to the Line22 SRL staff in charge of the website management, your personal data may be disclosed to or accessed by the following subjects:
Hosting provider: SiteGround Italia Srl – VAT IT 09659420963
Advertising network: Google Inc. (see above for details)
Newsletter service provider: AWeber Systems, Inc. (see above for details)
Public or private subjects in order to comply to the obligations provided for by law.
Rights of the users
In accordance with the articles 15 (Right of access), 16 (Right of rectification), 17 (Right to
cancellation), 18 (Right to limitation of treatment), 20 (Right to portability), 21 (Right to
opposition), 22 (Right to Opposition to the automated process), 77 (Right to file a complaint
to the Supervisory Authority) of the GDPR, the subject can exercise his rights by writing to
the e-mail address info@carbodydesign.com.
Please note that you have also the right to revoke your consent at any time by writing to info@carbodydesign.com.
Last Updated: May 24, 2018.
© 2004-2020 LINE22 SRL Società a Unico Socio - VAT IT 07892041000
FAQ
Privacy Policy (GDPR)
Impressum
Scroll To Top
Scroll To Bottom
